bulkfoods.com 2014-12-17

# Privacy Policy - Bulkfoods.com

Effective **01/01/2002**

  * ## **Privacy Policy Table Of Contents:**

    * Privacy Overview  
    * The Information That Is Collected  
    * How The Information is Utilized  
    * Data Security  
    * Children's Privacy  
    * How Information Can be Accessed Or Corrected  
    * How To Communicate About Privacy

* * *

##   
**Privacy Overview:**

Privacy is important. To better protect privacy this policy is provided explaining our online information practices and the choices that can be made about the way information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, it is available from a link positioned on the homepage of this internet website.

* * *

## **The Information That Is Collected:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages, products can be ordered, requests can be made, and registrations made to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name. Address, Email address, Phone number, Credit/Debit Card Information, etc.

On some pages, information can be submitted about other people. For example, if a gift is ordered online to be sent directly to the recipient, the recipients address will need to be submitted. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:  Name, Address, Phone Number, etc.

* * *

## **The Way The Information Is Utilized:**

The personal information provided when placing an order is needed to complete the order. The information is used to verify a persons identity. This information is used to process credit card information. The information is used to process and ship the order. The information is used to track orders when needed. Information is not shared with outside parties except to delivery service companies, credit card processing agencies and banks, and other companies as required or allowed by law. The information may be shared with firms including accountants, lawyers, government agencies and other parties as may be required or allowed by law. The information may be used by leased personnel or seasonal staffing companies and their personnel to process the order. The information may be used by contracted warehouses and freight lines necessary to fulfill the order in a timely manner.

The information provided about someone else for shipping purposes is used to ship the product and to confirm delivery. This information is not shared with outside parties except to the extent as described above.

Gift-cards can be personalized and sent along with products ordered for another person. Information provided to create gift-cards is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift.

Email addresses are used to answer emails received. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose except to provide important information about an order or which is believed to be of interest. Email addresses are shared with other parties, including internet service providers which are necessary to use in order to transmit e-mail replies.

Non-identifying and aggregate information may be used to better design our website and to share with advertisers and others. For example, an advertiser may be told that X number of individuals visited a certain area on the website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out the registration form.

Finally, the personal identifiable information provided is never used or shared in ways related or unrelated to the ones descried above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such uses.

* * *

## **Data Security:**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

* * *

## **Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

* * *

## **How Information Can be Accessed or Corrected:**

All personally identifiable information that is collected online and maintained can be accessed by saving email confirmations and/or making a request in writing. This procedure is used to better safeguard the information.

Factual errors in your personally identifiable information can be corrected by sending a request that credibly shows the errors.

To protect privacy and security, reasonable steps are taken to verify identity before making corrections.

* * *

## **Privacy Notice Revisions:**

To be able to continue to protect personal privacy and to conform to changing generally accepted practices the right is reserved to change this privacy notice. This privacy policy may need changed to comply with future government regulations which are constantly changing as the internet evolves. 

## **How To Communicate About Privacy:**

Should there be other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please mail a letter to our corporate office with the following caption. ATT: Privacy Manager BulkFoods.com 3040 Hill Avenue Toledo, Ohio 43607-2931
